坐进去 我想跟你坐靠近
Move over, I want to slide in close to you,
然后拍张照片放我们网站上
so we can take the picture for our new website.
你想跟我搞拉拉情就直接上
Look, if you want to get all lesbian with me, just go for it.
别用网站照片当借口
You don't have to pretend it's for the website.
我是说真的
It is.
顺带一提 09年凯蒂·佩里在高歌
And for the record, in 2009, when Katy Perry
"我亲了个女孩 我好喜欢"时
Kissed a girl and liked it
我也亲了 不过我不喜欢
I kissed one and didn't.
准备好了吗
Ready?
一 二 拍...
One... two... and...
-完美 -完美个屁
- Perfect. - Perfect?
这不是"请让我们承包孩子的生日派对"
This photo does not say "let us do your child's birthday party."
这是"我们是荒唐的摇滚乐团团员
It says "we're an AC/DC tribute band,
用可卡因当酬劳就行"
and you can pay us in cocaine."
奥列格
Oleg,
能帮我们拍张放网站的照片吗
will you take a picture of us for our website?
你知道你是请一名
You realize you just asked a man
只会拍自己下体的淫男拍照吗
who only takes pictures of his penis?
当然知道
Yes.
可他拍的照片光照适宜 聚焦准确
But it's always well-lit, and perfectly in focus.
包君满意
You won't be disappointed.
我给很多网站拍照过
I take lots of website pictures.
可我们没有只戴鸡面具跟穿胸罩啊
Yeah, but we're not wearing just bras and chicken masks.
有大把时间 会到的
We have time.
要不再考虑下刚才的"毒瘾浪女"照吧
Maybe we should rethink the "coke whore" picture.
晚安啦 女士们
Well, good night, ladies.
祝你们一夜好梦 别来无恙
Sleep tight, don't let the bed bugs bite.
我记得当年在纽约
And I remember a time in New York
这话是祝福语而不是担心有恙虫
when that was more cute than accurate.
-晚安 厄尔 -晚安
- Good night, Earl. - Good night.
厄尔 今晚的帐
Earl, I have come across
有六块钱对不上数
a $6 inaccuracy in tonight's total.
你得留下再算一次
You must go over all checks again.
阿憨 我都要准备回家了
Han, I'm just on my way home.
两点才下班呢
But it is not yet 2:00 A.M.
我不想当黑脸
I hate to play the heavy,
不过你得乖乖留下重新算好账
but you must sit down and go over checks again.
阿憨 我都七十五岁了
Han, I am 75 years old.
我老得拉屎都舍不得多擦两次屁股
I don't even have enough time left to wipe twice.
哎哟妈呀
Well, well.
女士您好
Hello there.
真绅士
Such a gentleman.
这小孩也好乖啊
And what a well-behaved boy.
女孩们在这啊
Oh, there are the girls.
苏菲 你好啊
Sophie, hello.
今天依旧光彩耀人啊
You look pretty.
我知道
Oh, I know.
真抱歉 厨房已经关了
Oh, sorry, the kitchen's closed.
-怎么会 -厨房本来是关了...
- What? - Kitchen was closed...
但厨房今始为君开
but can now be open again for such a beautiful woman.
你好 我是大厨
Hello. I am the chef.
烂戏又要上演了
Oh, here we go.
乌克兰要入侵波兰了
Ukraine's going to try to invade Poland.
诺曼底登陆2之大胸脯登陆
It's double D-day.
奥列格 苏菲是我们的邻居
Oleg, this is our neighbor, Sophie.
我想要先点一盘香肠
I would like to have a plate with sausage on it
然后我再慢慢看菜单
while I look over the menu.
亲娘咧
Yowza.
你就像个大号的维多利亚秘密女模啊
You are like someone super-sized Victoria's secret angel.
我好想要"挤塞儿"你的"膀衬"
I'd like to Gisele on your Bundchens.
有人不当 想当狗
You're going to act like a dog,
我就把你打成狗
I'll treat you like a dog.
他的"拍照"事业一去不复返了
Well, there goes his photography career.
你还要点香肠吗
Do you still want the sausage?
当然啊 干嘛迁怒无辜的香肠
Yes, of course. Why should sausage suffer?
你真是应对得宜啊
You know how to handle yourself.
叹为观止啊
Impressive.
刚就像是你在玩"剪掉 石砸 变态"游戏
That was like a game of "rock, paper, pervert."
苏菲 谢谢你特意过来
Sophie, thank you for coming in.
麦克斯和我想跟你谈谈接受邀请
Max and I wanted to talk to you about taking you up
去你的清洁公司工作的事情
on your offer to work for your cleaning company.
她想打工赚我们做网站的钱
Yeah, she wants to do it for money to pay for our website,
我想打工是因为
and I want to do it
我喜欢把陌生人家的药柜翻个底朝天
because I like rummaging through strangers' medicine cabinets.
你有打扫过房子吗
Have you cleaned houses before?
我有过别人打扫得非常干净的房子
Well, I had a house, and it was very clean.
无论你给我们什么任务 我们都会胜任
But whatever the task, you won't be sorry.
麦克斯跟我是黄金搭档
Max and I are a great team,
只要我们下定决心 就一定能完成任务
and when we set our mind to something, we accomplish it.
-如果你考虑给我们... -少废话
- And if you consider giving us... - Oh, stop.
这又不是牙科学院面试
This is not a dental school interview.
拜托 就是刷马桶的活儿
Come on, this is scrubbing toilets.
干还是不干
In or out?
加入 跟你干到底
We're in. All the way.
按我的经验 当要靠对方告诉你
In my experience, when someone has to tell you
他们已经"干到底"了
they're all the way in,
你只能祈祷他的舌头还算"能干"
you'd better hope their tongue works.
好黄好欢乐
So dirty.
我们明天就能开工
We can start tomorrow.
跟我们说个地点 我们会准时出现
Just tell us where to go, and we'll be there.
好的
Oh, okay.
首先走出家门
Well, uh, you walk out your door,
右转 上楼
you take right, you go upstairs,
打开我家门 然后打扫我的公寓
you open my door, and you clean my apartment.
这算试镜哦
Is audition.
我能像《名扬四海》那样 直接脱衣就好吗
Can't I just take off my shirt like in Fame?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
这是你的无骚扰开胃菜
Here is your non-sexual appetizer.
我们从新慢慢认识吧
You and I will start small.
意下如何
You like?
行
Yes.
乖狗狗 走开吧
Good boy. Now go.
被迫去打扫苏菲的公寓
Forced to clean Sophie's apartment?
这事越来越危险了
This is getting dicey.
很快的 我们就会被关在
Next thing you know, we're locked in a crate
运往远东的装货箱里
on our way to the far east.
麦克斯 我们得花钱做网站
Max, we're going to spend this money on our website.
那可是我们公司的未来呀
That's the future of our company.
可是未来在遥远的未来
But the future is so far in the future,
我现在需要花钱买真实的东西
and I need this money now for real stuff,
比如小熊软糖和眼线笔
like gummi bears and eye liner.
你觉得你将如何抵达未来
How do you think you get to the future?
马帝·麦克佛莱和一台德罗宁的跑车
Uh, Marty McFly and a Delorean?
再说了 我们目前还不需要网站
Besides, we don't need the website yet.
没有它 明天照样有人请我们做蛋糕
We got the birthday cupcake job tomorrow without it.
你觉得为什么会有人请我们
And where do you think we got that job?
我不知道 有仙女帮忙吗
I don't know, the job fairy?
干嘛啊 我本来对生意的事就不怎么上心
What? I don't pay attention to the business stuff.
我是在网站设计公司不小心听到
I got the order at the web design company
有人说他儿子要过五岁生日了
when I overheard someone say it was his son's fifth birthday.
真恶心 利用孩子来获利
Gross. Using children for your own profit.
挺有中国的风范嘛
Way to go, China.
我们准时到啦
Well, here we are.
这有需要昭告天下吗
Why is this big news?
进来吧
Come in.
如果今天一切顺利的话
So, if this all works out today,
就有两份工作等着你们
I have two possible jobs for you.
而且在同一栋楼里
Both at the same building.
两份 太棒了
Two? That's amazing.
这是我确保你们不毁坏
This is the only way that I can make sure
我公司好名声的唯一办法
that you don't ruin my company's good name.
毕竟"苏菲的选择" 是我辛苦打拼出来的
'Cause I work hard to build "Sophie's choice."
现在 你们一个去打扫厕所
Now, uh, one of you take bathroom
一个打扫客厅
and one of you take out here.
自己选一个吧
Who does which?
厕所 我就选厕所吧
Bathroom. I'm going to go with bathroom.
我喜欢有难度的活儿
I love a challenge.
如果达不到一尘不染 就没活儿
If not perfect clean, no job.
开工吧
Begin.
留神啦 女士们
Watch out, ladies.
我要给这间厕所一点"颜瞧"了
I'm about to go H.A.M on this b-room.
什么叫"颜瞧"
What is this "H.A.M"?
就是给点"颜射"瞧瞧
Hard as a mother.
麦克斯 我好喜欢你讲的荤段子
Max, I love when you're dirty.
令人激赏啊
Oh. Very impressive.
你打扫时力大如牛
You clean like bull.
咆哮出清洁的战歌
Roar of cleaning.
没什么啦
No big deal.
我六岁的时候就能举起沙发了
I was lifting up couches when I was six
当时是帮我妈妈找零钱和她男友的牙齿
to help my mom look for change and her boyfriend's tooth.
我快完工啦
I'm almost finished in here!
这家伙就喜欢屁事也要昭告天下 是吧
This one like to make big announcements about nothing, yes?
是啊
Yes.
你那电子烟好使吗
Hey, does that electric cigarette work?
挺好的
Yes, yeah.
我抽过7年的烟 直到12岁时我决定戒烟
I smoked for seven years, and then I quit when I was 12.
是啊 我不想还没青春期
Yeah, I didn't want to die of lung cancer
就死于肺癌
before I was teenager.
我能抽一口吗
Can I get a hit?
当然可以 试试吧
Oh, yeah, please, try.
我抽屉里还有很多呢
I have many more in the drawers.
我去同性恋游船上剥牡蛎的那个夏天抽过烟
I smoked the summer I shucked oysters on a gay cruise.
哇 真有"基"情啊
Ooh, glamorous.
快好了 倒数两分钟
Almost done. Two-minute warning.
准备好大开眼界吧
Be prepared to be amazed.
麦克斯 你不该抽烟 你会被...
Max, you shouldn't smoke. You'll get...
什么 电死吗
What, electrocuted?
电子烟真蠢
This is silly.
如果想"吸"根这么硬的玩意儿
If I'm going to suck on something this hard
又没半点爽感 去约会不就行了
and get no pleasure out of it, I should just date.
我觉得你会眼睛一亮的
I think you're going to be thrilled.
她弱爆了
Oh, she stinks.
这儿喷 那儿喷 她就是个喷头
Spritz, spritz. She is sprayer.
喷的全是镜子 马桶置之不理
All mirror, no toilet.
她在这种工作上还是个新手
Well, you know, she's sort of new to this kind of work.
她曾是个富家女
She was born rich,
可因为她爸拐了好多人的钱
but her father stole a bunch of money from people,
她才被赶出别墅 然后沦落至此
and she was thrown out of her townhouse and disgraced.
没错 她打扫时的确像个富家女
Yes, well, she clean like rich girl.
"大伙儿快看呀 我在干活呢
"Hey, everybody, look, look what I'm doing.
左喷喷 右喷喷"
Oh, spritz, spritz."
而你 虽然出身贫寒
See, you not born rich,
却有猛牛的霸气
and you... you're like "roar".
-没错吧 -不敢当
- Right? - Well.
她不擅长打扫 她有别的专长
Cleaning's not her thing, but she has other strengths.
反正我是没看见
Mm, I don't see them.
所以我们面试失败吗
Uh, so do we not have the job?
不 我给你工作
No, I give you job,
因为一头猛牛能顶俩姑娘
because one bull equal two girls.
可你非得搭上她 我就不明白了
But why you need her, I don't know.
你自己出来单干 钱只多不少
You can make much more money on your own.
话是没错 可我们是一个团队
Yeah, well, we're kind of a team.
听着 麦克斯 跟你说件事
Listen, Max. Let me tell you something.
她就像块石头 绑在你这个气球身上
She is like rock, tied to you, balloon.
她拖你的后腿
See, she hold you down.
一旦你摆脱她 就能...[一飞冲天]
You cut her loose, and...
她没有把我拖垮啦
Yeah, well, she's not weighing me down.
我曾经有个石头爱人
I had lover who was rock.
我跟他分手后 我就...
And I let him go, and...
我做完啦 而且我不得不说 那间厕所
I'm finished, and I have to say, that bathroom?
简直一尘不染
Nailed it.
别费口舌了 人家有眼看的
Don't push it. She saw it.
她根本就没看 我在镜子里看见你了
She barely looked at it. I saw you in the mirror.
你的眼睛完全没有往下看
Your eye never even looked down.
没错 那是因为这眼睛不能往下看
Yes, that's because this eye doesn't go down.
瞧 我尽力了
See, I'm trying.
我小时候发生过意外 眼睛有盲点
Yeah, I have blind spot from accident as child.
那年我六岁
When I was six years old,
在华沙的一家波兰
while working in Polish knock-off
山寨麦当劳店打工
of McDonalds in Warsaw,
我跌倒在炙热的"麦肉棒"上
I fell on hot McStick.
你怎么会跌在一根炙热的棒子上呢
How did you fall on a hot stick?
不是棒子炙热 是销量炙手可热的"麦肉棒"
Not a stick that is hot. A hot McStick.
是把肉串在棒子上 非常受欢迎呢
It's meat on a stick, and it's very popular.
一年两次 限时推出的
They only have it, like, two times a year.
就跟麦当劳猪排堡一样
It's like Mcribs.
苏菲 我真为你感到难过 这太惨了
Sophie, I'm so sorry, that's awful.
是啊 但我敢说那个"麦肉棒"一定很好吃吧
Yeah, but I bet that McStick thing is delicious.
的确
It is.
那给你生活制造了不少苦难吧
Well, that must have been hard.
我真佩服你的勇气
I admire your courage.
你是谁啊 联合国儿童基金会的辅导员吗
What are you, counsellor from UNICEF?
这面试你表现"真好"
You are acing this interview.
你知道我们是在哪儿吗
Do you know where we are?
这整栋楼住的全是模特
This whole building is models.
真是无巧不成书啊
Life is so funny.
想当年我还住曼哈顿时
When I lived in Manhattan,
天天来这里参加模特的派对
I used to come to model parties here all the time.
然而现在你却得清理他们的大便
And now you clean up their poop.
还真是无巧不成书啊
You're right. Life is funny.
明天要打扫的是楼上的公寓
Here's the apartment upstairs tomorrow.
-10J 就是这儿 -我看起来如何
- 10j. Here it is. - How do I look?
没准他是A & F圣诞节广告里的模特
Maybe he's the Abercrombie model from the Christmas ad
踩着白色的雪橇
in the white sleigh
穿着敞怀的绒绒外套 露出八块腹肌
with the open fleece jacket and the eight-pack.
貌似非你所想
I don't think it's him.
你好 我是胖子比尔
Hi, I'm Big Bill.
进来吧 姑娘们
Come on in, girlies.
你刚说几块腹肌来着
How many packs did you say?
你家真不错 哇
Oh, what a lovely... oh!
天啊
Oh, my God.
瞧 麦克斯 他是花样滑冰运动员
Look, Max, he's a figure skater.
慢慢欣赏 在脑中慢慢品味吧
Go ahead, take it all in.
谁会"不想欣赏"啊
How could you not?
没关系 我是个模特 早就习惯了
It's okay, I'm a model. I'm used to it.
我认得你了 你是那个胖子比尔
Hey, I know you. You're the Big Bill.
恶作剧贺卡上的那个人
You're the guy from the gag greeting cards.
没错 那张卡我一年能买二百万张呢
Yep. I sold 2 million of that particular card.
卡面正面写着"你的生活如履..."
On the front it says, "You're on,"
打开卡片就会看见
when you open it up...
-"薄冰" -没错
- "thin ice"! - Right.
我得回卧室换衣服离开了
Oh, I've got to go in my bedroom and change.
马上就好
I'll be right back.
哇 胖子比尔
Wow, Big Bill!
哇 风紧扯呼
No, big bye-bye.
此地不宜久留
We're not staying here.
墙上都敢挂出这种画
If that's what's on the wall,
谁知道他地板上能有什么
who knows what's on the floor.
或是地板下关着什么
Or trapped underneath it.
这工作环境真让人不舒服
This is an uncomfortable work environment.
你本来就得趴在地上刷马桶了
You were going to be on all fours scrubbing a toilet.
到死都不会是个舒服的工作环境呀
It was always going to be an uncomfortable work environment.
好吧 如果真不走
Okay, if we're staying,
你得想想这胖子是普通人的三倍大
that's three times the amount of man.
我们应该得到两倍的钱
We should get double the money.
我现在就打电话给苏菲
I'm calling Sophie right now
告诉她我们要涨钱
and telling her we should get more.
我不建议你跟苏菲抱怨
Um, I would not suggest you complain to Sophie.
这可不是个好主意
It's not a good idea.
为什么 有什么隐情吗
Why? Do you know something I don't?
她觉得你不会打扫
She thinks you don't know how to clean,
你只会喷来喷去
that you spritz, spritz.
那她怎么评价你的打扫能力
And what does she say about your cleaning skills?
力大如牛 效率奇高
I'm a bull and I roar.
我就知道她不喜欢我
I knew she didn't like me.
眼里只看得到你的好
She only has eye for you.
谁管她怎么想 今天好好打扫就行了
Who cares what she thinks. Just clean better today.
客厅归你 厕所归我
You do the living room. I'll do the bathroom.
不 厕所归我 我要证明给她看
No, I'll do the bathroom, just to prove a point.
再一次证明
I mean, reprove it.
感觉就像当年
This is just like when
他们让我重考高考一样
they made me take the S.A.T.S again,
得证明自己不是靠隔壁的亚洲人
away from all the Asian kids.
我的神呀
Oh! Oh, my God!
你叫个屁啊
Why are you freaking out?
他的裸体你不是早见过了吗
You've already seen him naked.
不是他啦
It's not him.
你见过这么大的马桶吗
Have you seen the size of this toilet?
这个坑真他妈大呀
That is a big-ass toilet.
真正的大坑啊
Literally.
麦克斯 我做完了
Max, I'm finished.
这地板干净到都能在上面吃饭了
The floor is so clean you could eat off it,
那胖子肯定会这么做的
and I'm sure he will.
快进来 我想让你见证一下
Come on in, I want you to see it.
别 别 别 别
No, no, no, no, no, no.
下去 下去 快停下来
Go down, go down, stop.
算啦 不需要你来见证了 一切顺利
Never mind! Don't need you to see it. Everything's okay.
外面打扫得怎么样了
How's it going out there?
你是羊水破了 还是能尿出蓝精灵尿啊
Either your water just broke, or you pee like a smurf.
我的鞋
My shoes.
不是吧 你一次冲了整卷厕纸啊
No, you did not flush a whole roll of paper towels.
不是吧 这种时候你还这语气指责我
No, you did not just use that tone with me
我的好鞋都被弄湿了
when my good shoes are wet.
关掉水阀
Shut off the valve.
什么水阀
The valve?
天啊 你是怎么搞的
Oh, God, what is wrong with you?
怎么会连马桶水阀在哪里都不知道啊
How can you not know where a toilet valve is?
我是个富家女好吗
I was rich.
但你得承认 那镜子
But you have to admit, the mirror?
一尘不染哟
Nailed it.
起来 你个懒货
Wake up, you lazy bitch!
-什么 -火
- What? - Fire!
工作付之一炬了吗 就因为个马桶啊
I'm fired? Why, because of the toilet?
你看看烤箱 我们的小蛋糕
Look at the oven, the cupcakes.
抱歉 我睡着了
I'm sorry. I fell asleep.
我刚只是想躺个五分钟
I was just going to lay down for five minutes.
我出门买牛奶前
I asked you to do one thing
就拜托你做这么一件事
while I went out to get more milk...
把小蛋糕从烤箱里拿出来
Take the cupcakes out of the oven.
"生日快乐 孩子 这是麦克斯自制小蛋糕
"Happy Birthday, kids. From Max's homemade cupcakes.
如想更了解我们 及我们的招牌碳烤蛋糕
You can learn more about us and our blackened cupcakes
请点击我们的高价网站"
on our expensive website."
对不起 麦克斯
I'm sorry, Max.
打扫了那么久 我真得睡一下[西语]
I just really needed a little siesta after all that cleaning.
为什么你的西语这么好 打扫却这么烂啊
How are you so good at Spanish and so bad at cleaning?
这是什么味道
What is that smell?
我都抓起钱包要避难了
I grabbed my purse and ran.
卡洛琳把蛋糕烤糊了
Caroline burned cupcakes.
真可怜
Oh, so sad.
看看这些烤糊的蛋糕
Look at all those burnt cakes.
发生什么事了
What happened here?
发生了点小意外
Just a little mishap.
今天打扫厕所太累了
I was so tired from cleaning that bathroom earlier,
我就跑去躺个五分钟
that I laid my head down for five minutes
没想到就睡过头了
and ended up falling asleep.
好可惜哟
Such a shame.
瞧 麦克斯
Oh, look Max.
这些蛋糕 就跟"石头"一样硬
These cupcakes, they're hard as rocks.
你只需
All you have to do
扔掉石头 就可以...
is throw the rock away, and whee!
我觉得苏菲不喜欢我
I don't think Sophie likes me.
你瞎说什么 她可喜欢你了
What are you talking about? She loves you.
她眼睛并非有盲点而看不见
No. I don't think she has a blind spot.
完全就只是单纯对我有意见
I think she has a blonde spot... for me.
我觉得我们找到
Well, I think we've found the place
红牛墓场了
where red bulls come to die.
真是的 怎么都没人邀请我来这种派对呢
Man, why do I never get invited to parties like this?
快看 知道这意味着什么吗
Look. Do you know what that means?
知道 这栋楼极度缺少上衣
Yeah, this building has a real shirt shortage.
天啊 你觉得这会是
Oh, my God, do you think
A & F模特的公寓吗
this might be the Abercrombie model's apartment?
我持怀疑态度
I doubt it's the Abercrombie model's apartment.
还给咱们留了张条
Here's a note.
是给"清洁土人"
It's addressed to "Cleaning dood,"
把"工人"写成"土人"
"Dude" Spelled "D-o-o-d."
这肯定是模特儿的公寓啦
It definitely might be the Abercrombie model's apartment.
"来了就叫醒我吧" 他说让咱们叫醒他呢
"Wake me when you get here." He wants us to wake him.
你觉得他是裸睡吗
So, do you think he sleeps in the nude?
对 "果睡" "赤果果"
Yeah, "Nood", "N-o-o-d."
快走 咱们去看看
Come on, let's go look.
哎哟 所以现在看这个家伙的裸体
Oh, oh, oh, so what, seeing this guy naked
就不算是"不舒服的工作环境"吗
is no longer an "uncomfortable work environment"?
还是不舒服啊
It's still uncomfortable,
不过是爽得让人不舒服
but in that exciting uncomfortable way.
我觉得就是他了
I think it is him.
在A & F广告中露腹肌的那个人
It's the guy who put the "abs" In Abercrombie.
而且他裸睡 撩人的裸体啊
And he's naked. The good naked.
我们该把床单撩起来吗
Should we lift the sheet?
此时不撩更待何时 我心里早把它撩开了
Why not? I already lifted it in my mind.
麦克斯 这里交给我吧
Max, I got this.
你开始打扫外面吧
You start cleaning up the mess out there.
不 你去打扫外面 我来处理这里
No, you start cleaning the mess out there... I got this.
卧室连着厕所
The bedroom's attached to the bathroom,
我总是打扫厕所 而且他还是我喜欢的类型
and I always do the bathrooms, and he's my ideal type.
你说的"打扫"厕所 是指让厕所发大水吗
And by "doing" the bathrooms do you mean flooding them,
"喜欢的类型"是指不省人事的吗
and by "Ideal type," do you mean unconscious?
我们去外面说
We can talk about this out here.
你会弄醒他的
You're going to wake him.
叫醒他本来就是活的一部分
That's what we're supposed to do.
不过你一如往常 不想干活
But as usual, you don't want to do the job.
你怎么了 今天这么奇怪
What's wrong with you? You're acting weird.
为什么我要干所有的重活
Well, why should I have to do all the heavy lifting
而你又能小睡 又能免费"赏鸟"
while you just get to nap and see free model penis?
所有的重活 谁说的
All the heavy lifting? Where'd you get that from?
没谁
No one.
苏菲
Sophie.
我就知道她不喜欢我
I knew she didn't like me.
这跟她喜不喜欢你无关
It's not that she doesn't like you,
她觉得你...
she just doesn't think you're...
怎么 一事无成吗
What? Doing anything?
她觉得我没有出力吗
She thinks I'm not pulling my weight?
她觉得我是累赘是吧
She thinks I'm a dead weight?
不是累赘 更像是...石头
Not dead weight, more like... a rock...
而我是气球
to my balloon.
那是什么鬼 某种波兰俳句吗
What is that, some kind of Polish haiku?
那到底什么意思啊
What does that even mean?
她觉得我如果剪断绑石头的绳子 我就能...
She thinks if I cut the rock loose, I'll go...
所以你要抛下我 去跟一个
Wait, so you're siding with a woman
才认识一周的女人结盟吗
you met a week ago over me?
我没有跟任何人结盟 我只是说...
I'm not siding with anyone. I'm just saying...
我懂了 就是"百般刁难富家女"嘛
I know what this is. This is "pick on the rich girl."
这是穷人的自卑心作祟
It's a poverty smackdown.
我在她厕所打扫时 就听见你俩说话了
I heard you two talking while I was in her bathroom,
左喷喷右喷喷
spritz spritzing.
你觉得所有的活都是你干的
You think you do everything?
好啊 那你全干吧
Fine, do everything.
这地方全归你这"气球"
You can "balloon" All over this place,
因为我这块"石头"要走了
'cause the "rock" Is leaving.
谁呀
Who is it?
你才是石头 我是气球
You're the rock! I'm the balloon!
要不是我拯救你这块消极的臭石头
Without me lifting you out of your negative rockness,
你哪来的小蛋糕生意啊
you wouldn't even have a cupcake business.
咱们能有今天 全是我的功劳
I'm the reason we even have cupcake jobs.
都你的功劳是吗
Oh, oh, you're the reason?
那谁在你昨晚呼呼大睡时 彻夜不眠
Who stayed up all last night baking 24 more cupcakes
重烤了二十四个蛋糕呢
while you were sleeping?
是你 又是谁今早在你倒头大睡时
You did. And who delivered the cupcakes this morning
去送这二十四个蛋糕呢
while you were sleeping?
是我 我这个气球
I did. Me. The balloon.
我飘去收了靠我努力赚钱付的网站
I floated over there and got paid for the job that I got us
给我们找来的工作工资
from the website that I'm trying to pay for.
现在 我要飘过走廊
And now, I'm going to float down this hall
去叫醒那位帅哥 因为跟你和
and wake the hot model up 'cause, contrary to what you
你那位穷人朋友想的相反
and your poverty gal-pal might think,
我总是能做好我的本职工作
I always do the job I'm hired for.
不 我要去叫醒他
Oh, no! I am going to wake him up.
免费"赏鸟"是我干所有的活和
Free model penis is my reward for doing everything
被你这样的石头拖累的奖励
and being tied to a rock like you.
看见没 我甩不开你 因为你才是石头
Oh, see? I can't get away, because you're the rock
你拖累了我这个气球
and you're heavier than my balloon.
住手
Hey, stop!
我是叫你们来打扫
This is cleaning job,
不是玩什么美女摔跤
not gorgeous ladies of wrestling.
幸好我路过来看下你们
Good thing I stopped by to check on you.
-这是怎么回事 -你来解释
- What is all this? - You explain it.
我要去把帅哥叫醒
I'm going to go wake the hot model up.
他留了张纸条 我只是尽本分而已
He left a note. Just doing my job.
一如往常的尽本分
As usual.
你觉得我拖了麦克斯的后腿吗
So, you think I'm holding Max back?
这是哪门子问题啊
What kind of question is this?
没错
Yes.
你错了 我们是黄金搭档
Well, you're wrong. We're a great team.
没错 是有些事情她比我擅长
And, yes, there are some things she's better at.
但我也有做得比她更好的地方
But there are other areas where I excel.
反正我是没看见
Well, I don't see them.
鼠目寸光的人有盲点也正常
That's probably because of your eye.
你把他叫醒了吗
Did you wake him up?
没有 他貌似是死了
Uh, no. I think he might be dead.
天啊 别是帅的这个啊
Oh, no, not the hot one!
他是我的最爱
Aw, he's my favorite.
我还要靠他在点评网给我好评呢
This is all I need on Yelp.
我们打电话叫救护车吧
We should call 911.
不必 我有办法
No, I got it.
你要干什么
What are you going to do?
我要给他做人工呼吸
I'm going to give him mouth-to-mouth.
我还真不知道人工呼吸要用到舌头的
I didn't know there was so much tongue involved.
不行啊
This is not working.
不过 我知道他还活着
But, you know what? I know he's still alive,
因为他的男根正顶着我的水帘洞
because his manhood is knocking on my lady door.
他肯定是吃了太多桌子上的药片
He must have taken too many of those pills on the table.
药片 我有办法了
Pills? I got this.
麦克斯 去拿点双氧水
Max, go get some hydrogen peroxide.
-苏菲 麻烦让开 -好的
- Sophie, step aside, now. - Oh, all right.
你真的知道自己在干嘛吗
You sure you know what you're doing?
我朋友坎迪丝大学时有过三次服药过量
My friend Candace Travelstead od'd like three times in college,
我把她救回来过"两次"
and I brought her back twice.
交给你了
There you go.
把他弄醒
Bring him up.
麦克斯 你把他的头往后拉 弄开他的嘴巴
Max, you hold his head back, open his mouth.
后退
Back up.
我开始看出你的价值了
I'm starting to see your worth.
干嘛 你就像个地铁痴汉
What? You're being subway creepy.
不得不说 当你用力揍
I have to say, when you were punching
那个半死模特的胃时
that almost-dead guy in the stomach,
还真像是气球之举
that was a serious balloon move.
其实我们都是气球
The truth is, we're both balloons.
对 可我的比你的酷多了
Yeah, but mine is, like, way cooler than yours.
就好比那种从来不会漏气的银色气球
It's like one of those silver ones that never goes out of air.
那种气球都不生产了 它们有毒
They don't make those anymore. They're toxic.
正是在下
Exactly.
麦克斯 我知道你是保护我不让我进厨房
Max, you know you won't let me come into the kitchen
帮忙烘培的 对吧
and help you bake, right?
你也懂我心里清楚 没有你
And you know that I know that without you,
才不会有什么"仙女"赐给我们工作的吧
the job fairy would never show up, right?
如果有天你需要人帮忙烘焙 我乐意之至
But if you ever need me to help you bake, I could.
没关系
No, it's cool.
你做你的 我做我的
You do your thing, I'll do mine.
把手机拿出来
Hey, get your phone.
我们应该记录这个"起死回生"的一刻
We should capture this near-death victory moment
作为我们的网站图片
as our website picture.
就是
Totally.
数到三 然后想"我们挣了两百块哦"
On the count of three, think..."we made $200."
一 二
One... two...
等等
Hold up.
先生 如果你不想断手断脚的回家
Sir, if you want to go home with that hand,
快把淫手从我屁股上挪开
get it off my ass.
好了 三
Okay, three.